Guide to the American Business Consultants, Inc. Counterattack: Research Files TAM 148
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series 50: Organizations, Miscellaneous (arranged alphabetically); see also, series 15: Organizations, Miscellaneous - arranged by file#.
  - National Council of Churches, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 50-124)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 36, Folder 50-126)
  - *National Lawyers Guild, 1954-1957 (Box 36, Folder 50-127)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1946-1957 (Box 36, Folder 50-128)
  - Institute for the Study of the USSR, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-129)
  - New School for Social Research, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 50-130)
  - New York State Education, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-131)
  - Northern Neighbors, 1946-1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-132)
  - Passports, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-133)
  - Peru, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-134)
  - Pizer, Morris; United Furniture Workers, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 50-135)
  - Missing folder, undated (Box 36, Folder 50-136)
  - Polaris - Atomic Power, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 50-137)
  - Powell-Schuman Defense Fund, 1950-1957 (Box 36, Folder 50-138)
  - Princeton University, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-139)
  - Religion, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-140)
  - Religious Freedom Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-141)
  - Religious Freedom News, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 50-142)
  - Retail Clerks International Union, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-143)
  - Roosevelt University, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-144)
  - Russia & satellites - uprisings, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 50-145)
  - Schwarz, Dr. Fred C., 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-146)
  - Security, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-147)
  - Senate Internal Security, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 50-148)
  - Servicemen's Defense Committee, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-149)
  - Shaw, Irwin, 1949-1951 (Box 36, Folder 50-150)
  - Sheiner, Leo, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-15)
  - Socialist Unity Forum, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 50-152)
  - Socialist Youth Committee of Chicago, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-153)
  - *Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1951-1954 (Box 36, Folder 50-154)
  - Soviet Elections, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-155)
  - Soviet Periodicals, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 50-156)
  - Stern, Alfred, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 50-157)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 50-158)
  - Summit Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 50-159)
- Series 99: Additional Miscellaneous Files
  NOTE: The folders in the remaining boxes (39-44) have not been evaluated for marking with either an (*) denoting especially rich materials, such as undercover reports, or a (+) denoting materials created by right-wing individuals or organizations. (Boxes 37, 38; unprocessed boxes 39-48 to be added to this series)
  - A. A. C. Book List, 1944, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Action Books, 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1a)
  - Advance Youth Organization, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1b)
  - African American Institute, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - African Fair Inc., 1960 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Afro-Asian Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Alabama Christian movement for Human Rights, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - All Russian Liberation Committee, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Amerasia, 1946-1950 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - American Assembly, 1957-1965 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - American Association for the United Nations, 1955-1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1949-1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - American Association of University Women, 1955-1962 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - *American Bar Association, 1951-1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - American Bar Association Syllabus*, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - American Broadcasting Company- Alger Hiss Broadcast, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - American Christian Palestine Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - * American Civil Liberties Union, 1920-1968 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, Inc., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - American Committee for Liberation, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - American Committee for the Protection opf the Foreign Born, 1955-1960 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - American Committee on Africa, 1959-1963 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - American Committte to Free Cuba, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - American Committee to Improve our Neighborhood, 1955-1960 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - American Communication Association, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - American Council for Judaism, 1955-1959 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - American Council of Christian Churches, 1956-1959 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - American Council of Voluntary agencies, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - American Council on Education, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1952-1960 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - American Federation of radio and Television Artists, 1952-1957 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - American Field Service, 1955-1960 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - American Forum for socialist Education, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - American Freedom from Hunger Foundation, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - American Freedom of Residence Fund, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - American Friends of Russian Freedom, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - * American Friends Service Committee, 1935-1965 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - American Fund for Public Service, 1931-1934 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - American Heritage Foundation (1950's?), undated (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - American Institute of Religion, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1962-1965 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - * American League against War and Fascism, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - American Library Association- Bookburning; Blackout, 1955-1964 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - American Nazi Party, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - American Negro Conference on Africa, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - American Parents Committee, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - American Peace Crusade, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - American Public Relations Forum, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - American Religious Town Hall Meeting (TV show), 1958 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - American Society for Industrial Security*, 1957-1959 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1947-1960 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - American Veterans Elbe River Linkup, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - American Veterans World War II, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - American Writers Association, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, 1957-1963 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - * Americans for Democratic Action, 1949-1965 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Americans for National Security, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Americans Underground, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - AMTORG, 1930, 1952, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Anti-anti-communists, 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Anti-communist Liason, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Anti-Communist Organizations (miscellaneous), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - * Anti-Defamation League, 1947-1965 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Appeasers and Appeasement, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - Area Redevelopment, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Arkansas Legislative Council, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Arms of Friendship, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Army (Department Organization), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Artists' Committee to Free Siqueros, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - Artists Letter Fund (disarmament), 1962 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - Assembly of Unrepresented People, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - Atlantic Union, 1955-1963 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - Association for Family Living, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - Atomic Energy Agency, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - * Attorney General Subversive Front List, 1948-1964 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - Authors League of America, 1952-1957 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - * Bandung Conference, 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Adults (study course), 1964 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Baptist World Alliance, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Bilderberg Group: 1957 St. Simon Island Conference, 1957-1964 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Bill of Rights Conference, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - John Birch Society, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Black Liberation Front, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Book Find Club, 1945-1950 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Books- How Conservative Books are Banned in Libraries, 1951-1961 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Branden Clemency Appeal, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 10,11)
  - Brainwashing, 1952-1960 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Bricker Amendment, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Broadview Research Corporation, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - California Free Enterprise Association, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Captive Nations Week, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1955-1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Catholic Council on Civil Liberties, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Catholic Freedom Foundation, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Cathoilic Interracial Council, 1958-1964 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Center for Research on Conflict/Resolution, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Chautauqua, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - China: Reasons for the Loss of, 1951, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Christian Amendment Movement, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Christian Century, 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Christian Democratic Movement of Cuba, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - * Christian Faith and Life Community (Laos House), 1960 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1939-1961 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Christ's Mission (Christian Heritage, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - * Churchman, 1959-1962 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - * Church Peace Mission, 1950-1958 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Church Peace Union, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Citizens Committee for Federal Aid for Public Schools, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Citizens Committee fopr International Development, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Citizens Councils, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Citizens Defense Fund, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Citizens for Freedom, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Citizens United Press, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Civic Research Bureau- "State of Affairs", 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Civil Rights Congress, 1946-1951 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Civil Rights (Presidential Commission), 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Clergyman's Emergency Committee, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Columbia Broadcast System, 1952-1962 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Columbia Council for the Gradualist Way to Peace, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Cold War Council (Los Angeles), 1962 (Box 38, Folder 51, 52)
  - Commission on Freedom of the Press, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Committe for a Review of Our China Policy, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Committe for Economic Development, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Committe for Fundamental American Freedoms, Inc, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Committe for International Growth, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Committe for Non-violent Action, 1960-1963 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - Committee for Peaceful Alternatives to the Atlantic Poact, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Committe for Piullion Resolution, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Committee for Protection of Children from Nuclear Fallout, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Committe for Special Medical Aid to Cuba, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Committe for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Committee for Welfare, Education and Legal Defense (WELD), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Committee for World Development and World Disarmament, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Committee of Arts, Letters, and Sciences, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Committee of One Million, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Committee on Captive Nations, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - *Committee on Electoral College Reform, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Committee on Government Security, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Committee on Present Danger, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Committee on University and World Affairs, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Committe to aid the Monroe Defendants, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Committee to WARN of the Arrival of Communist Merchandise on the Local Scene, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - Common Council for American Unity, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - *Communism in Florida, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Communist Gift Organizations, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Communist Party Leaders Abroad, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - Communists: Legal Action Against, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - *Concern (Methodist Publication), 1962 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Concerned White Citizens of Alabama, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Conference for Legislation in the National Interest, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - Conference of Greater New York Peace Groups, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - Conference on Economic Progress, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Conference on Voting Restrictions in Southern States, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - Congress of Conservatives 1965, undated (Box 38, Folder 89)
  - Congress of Industial Organizations (CIO), 1953 (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - *Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1958-1964 (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - *Conlon Associates (San Fransisco), 1959-1960 (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - *Conservative Alliance, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Constitution Party of Florida, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 94)
  - Constitutional Amendments (Court of the Union), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 95)
  - ConstitutionalConservative Movement in the United States, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 96)
  - Conservative Action, Inc, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 97)
  - Consultative Conference on Desegregation, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 98)
  - Consumers Union, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 99)
  - Council for Basic Education- Bulletin, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 100)
  - Council on African Affairs, 1946, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 101)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 102)
  - *Council on World Affairs, 1960-1963 (Box 38, Folder 103)
  - *Convicted Communists, 1951-1958 (Box 38, Folder 104)
  - Critical Issues Coucil, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 105)
  - Christian Rural Overseas Program (CROP), 1964 (Box 38, Folder 106)
  - *Eastern, PA and Phillipsburg, NJ Investigation, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 107)
  - Educational Programs- International, 1957, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 108)
  - Eisenhower Doctrine, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 109)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1955, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 110)
  - *Eisenhower Statements, 1952, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 111)
  - Fact, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1954, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1935-1966 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Fellow Traveler, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Fifth Amendment, 1951-1957 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Fifth Amendment Pleaders, 1951-1956 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Florida's Communism Course, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Florida Council on Human Relations, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Fluoridation, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Focus, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - For America, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Forced Repatriation, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation and Adjuncts, 1951-1964 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Aid-India, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1960-1962 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Forensic Foundation, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Fort Monmouth Radar, 1953-1954, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order (FRASCO), 1956-1964 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Foundations, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Freedom Academy, 1961-1965 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Freedom Agenda, 1954-1956 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Freedom House, 1959-1965 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Freedom Medal Awards, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Free World Committee, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Friends of the First Amendment, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Friends- Yearly Quaker Meetings, etc., 1963 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Friendship Book (San Francisco), 1953 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Front Organizations, 1943-1956 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Fox Boston Post Series on Harvard, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1955-1963 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Gaither Report, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Gallup Poll- McCarthy Ratings, 1953-1962 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Genocide Treaty, 1950-1951 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Grass Roots League, 1953-1959 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Group Investigation Associates (Boston,MA), 1965 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Group Research, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Harvard University, 1951-1961 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Haryou, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Hate Groups, 1953-1959 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Highlander Folk School, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Hugh Moore Fund, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Humanity Guild, Inc., 1961-1962, undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Hungarian Uprising, 1956-1962 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Iberica, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Inclosure Number 76388, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - The Independent (Formerly: Expose), 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Independent Socialist Electoral Ticket, undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1959-1963 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Institute for Defense Analysis, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Institute for International Order, 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1951-1960 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Institute on Internal Education, 1933, 1955-1959 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Inter-American Association, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Interarmco, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Internal Security Act (1950), 1951-1955 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - International Labor Defense, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - International Labor Organization, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - International Union of Mill, Mine, and Smelter Workers, 1955-1960 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - International Union of Students, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1949-1956 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Koinonia Foundation, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Labor Youth League, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1961-1965 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - League of Women Voters, 1954-1965 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Liberalism- General Definitions, etc., 1956-1961 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Liberation Committee for Africa, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Lifeline Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Little Rock, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Logan Act of 1799, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - Loyalty Oath, 1959-1965 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Mallory Decision, 1957-1960 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - The Marin Story, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Marzani and Munsell, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Medical Aid to Cuba Committee, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health, 1954-1962 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Methodist Church- Manual on Christian Concerns, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Methodist Federation of Socialist Action, 1928-1965 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Milwaukee, WI As Hoc Committee (pro-Castro), 1961 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Minority of One, 1961-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - The Nation, 1952-1965 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - National Alliance of Russian Solidarists (NTS), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - National Assembly for Democratic Rights, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1955-1965 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - National Assembly of Social Workers, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - National Broadcasting Company- social content programs, etc., 1961 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - National Center for Education in Politics, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - National Citizens Commission for Public Schools, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - National Guardian, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - National Indignation Convention, 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - National Information Bureau, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - National Institute of Social Relations, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1953-1958 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - National Maritime Union, 1942-1960 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - National Municipal League, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Negro National Labor Council, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - National Party of the U.S.A., 1958 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - National Planning Association, 1957-1964 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - National Precinct Workers, Inc. (Chicago), 1964 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - National Renaissance Party, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - National Reprint Service, 1950-1955 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - National Right to Work Committee, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - National Security Council, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - National Service Board for Religious Objectors, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - National Service Corps, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - National States Right Party (The Thunderbolt), 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - National Student Association, 1957-1965 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - National Student Committee for the Loyalty Oath, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - National Student Federation, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Nationwide Insurance (formerly Farm Bureau Insurance), 1955, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Negro American Labor Council, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Neighbors, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Nieman Foundation (Harvard), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - New England Party of Labor, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - New Leader, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - New World Review, 1957-1964 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - New York Committee for the General Strike for Peace, 1961-1962 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - New York Peace Information Center, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Newsweek, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Non-violent Committee for Cuban Independence, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - National Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Northern League, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Northern Student Movement, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Duplicate Reports AA-AH (includes Dr. Harold Aaron), 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Duplicate Reports AI-AP (includes American Civil Liberties Union, American Russian Institute, Antioch College), 1949-1955 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Duplicate Reports AQ-AZ (includes Max Ascoli, educator and editor), 1949-1954 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Duplicate Reports BA-BH (includes Charlotta Bass and Howard Bay), 1948-1953 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Duplicate Reports BI-BP (includes Bruce Bliven, Jr. and Book Find Club), 1948-1962 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Duplicate Reports BR-BZ (includes Millen Bramd, author; Oscar Brand, Henrietta Buckmaster, Robert (William) Burke), 1948-1955 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Duplicate Reports Brewers, 1945-1958 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Duplicate Reports Buck, Pearl S., 1950-1955 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Duplicate Reports CA-CH (includes Nicholas Carnes; "Case of the Loaded Mike," a radio play; Charlie Chaplin; Allen Chase), 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 1)